<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://ychen884.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml"/><link href="https://ychen884.github.io/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en"/><updated>2023-08-24T22:50:20+00:00</updated><id>https://ychen884.github.io/feed.xml</id><title type="html">blank</title><subtitle>A simple, whitespace theme for academics. Based on [*folio](https://github.com/bogoli/-folio) design. </subtitle><entry><title type="html">My Courses &amp;amp; Grades in UW-Madison</title><link href="https://ychen884.github.io/blog/2023/undergradCourses/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="My Courses &amp;amp; Grades in UW-Madison"/><published>2023-08-20T18:37:00+00:00</published><updated>2023-08-20T18:37:00+00:00</updated><id>https://ychen884.github.io/blog/2023/undergradCourses</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://ychen884.github.io/blog/2023/undergradCourses/"><![CDATA[ <p>The University of Wisconsin-Madison offers an exceptional Computer Science track for undergraduate students, enabling them to delve into various fields within the discipline. During my undergraduate studies, I concentrated on system courses, which allowed me to gain valuable insights into this specialized area.</p> <p>Below is a breakdown of the courses I undertook at UW-Madison. The advanced courses have been highlighted at the beginning of the list for emphasis. I am profoundly grateful to my instructors, whose dedication and passion have significantly shaped my academic journey. Their guidance, coupled with my relentless hard work and consistent efforts, has truly made a difference in my education.</p> <p>The courses at UW-Madison are categorized into three distinct levels:</p> <p>Elementary (E): Typically, entry-level courses designed for freshmen and sophomores. Intermediate (I): These courses are aimed at students in their sophomore to junior years. Advanced (A): Targeted at students in their junior to senior years, these courses focus on more specialized and complex topics. The education I received at UW-Madison has not only broadened my knowledge but also laid a solid foundation for my future pursuits in the field of Computer Science.</p> <table data-toggle="table" data-url="/assets/json/table_data.json"> <thead> <tr> <th data-field="Courses">Courses</th> <th data-field="Description">Description</th> <th data-field="Final Grade">Final Grade</th> </tr> </thead> </table> <p></p> ]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="Study"/><category term="UW-Madison"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[:) I enjoy all the courses I took in UW-Madison.]]></summary></entry></feed>